welcome to category 5 technology TV
カテゴリ5技術テレビへようこそ
episode number 383 for tuesday the 20th
火曜日のためのエピソード番号383 20日
of January 2015 i'm your host Robbie
2015年1月 の 私は あなたのホスト ロビー よ
Ferguson good to have you here nice to
ファーガソンはここにあなたにいいことがありがとう
see so many familiar faces in the chat
チャットでとても親しみやすい顔を見る
room and a couple people who haven't
部屋とカップルのない人
been around lately and a few new people
最近周りにいた
as well we're gonna say hello to you in
私たちはあなたにこんにちはを言うつもりです
in a little bits time tonight though
今夜は少しでも 時間がかかる
we've got a fairly packed show for you
我々はあなたのためにかなりパックされたショーを持っている
we're going to be speaking with Kelly
私たちはケリーと話すつもりです
lastly in from memories of me Hillary's
私の記憶から最後にヒラリーの
actually over in the interview studio
実際に面接スタジオで
right now getting ready for that
今すぐ準備ができている
interview we're gonna be talking about
インタビュー我々はつもりの話をされています
the digital time capsule service that
デジタルタイムカプセルサービスは、
Kelly has launched in order to give us a
ケリーは私たちに
way to reach out to those that we love I
私たちが愛する人たちに手を差し伸べる方法
should something happen to us of a
何かが私たちの
tragedy Sasha's in Jamaica tonight so we
悲劇サシャは今夜ジャマイカにいるので
threw the magic of television are able
テレビの魔法を投げたことができる
to throw it over to her Sasha in the
彼女のサシャに
newsroom Hey hi raha hai Ellery awesome
ニュースルームHey hi raha hai Ellery素晴らしい
here in Jamaica this is a soulless
ここジャマイカでは、これは魂がない
history all right
歴史は大丈夫
here's what's coming up in the category
ここでは、カテゴリに登場するものがあります
5 TV news room the city of Munich has
5テレビニュースルームミュンヘンの街には
joined the document foundation advisory
文書基盤アドバイザリに参加しました
board Linux Mint has announced that a
Linux Mintは、
new pc in its mint box line of pcs is
PCのミントボックスラインの新しいPC は
coming in the spring the myth box mini
春に来る神話ボックスミニ
Google is ending its sales of its google
GoogleはGoogleの販売を終了する
glass eyewear German researchers have
ガラスの眼鏡ドイツの研究者は
built shoe size devices that harvest
収穫した靴のサイズのデバイスを構築
power from the act of walking who major
誰が主要な歩行の行為からの電力
retailers are in Canada are calling it
カナダの小売業者はそれを呼んでいる
quits this week in Canada installing
今週はカナダでのインストールをやめる
computer programs without consent
同意なしにコンピュータプログラム
consent became a civil offense
同意は民事犯罪になった
punishable by fines and one of the most
罰金に処罰され、最も罰金の1つ
glorious near misses in the history of
歴史の中で輝かしいニアミス
British exploration beacon to has been
英国の探査ビーコンにされている
found stick around the full details are
完全な詳細の周りにスティックが見つかりました
coming up later in the show
ショーの後で登場する
this is category 5 technology TV
これはカテゴリ5の技術テレビです
starring
主演
Sasha donatus
サシャ・ドナトゥス
Hillary rumble
ヒラリー・ランブル
Christo wells
クリストウェルズ
and kid
子供
and your host Ravi Ferguson
あなたのホストラビ・ファーガソン
this category 5 technology TV thanks for
このカテゴリ5技術テレビのおかげで
being here tonight first of all I'm not
今夜ここにいるのはまず私はいない
used to be your way over there how are
そこにあなたの道があった
you hell I'm under we can hear her we
あなたは地獄です私たちは彼女のことを聞くことができます
can't see her but there you go she's
彼女を見ることはできませんが、そこには彼女が行く
here we're gonna be throwing over to her
ここで私たちは彼女に投げつけられるつもりです
in just a couple minutes time category
ほんの数分の時間カテゴリで
five TV as a member of the tech podcast
技術ポッドキャストのメンバーとして5つのテレビ
network check them out at five not TV /
ネットワークではない5時にそれらをチェックアウトテレビ /
and also the American Association of
また、
Internet no the International
インターネットはインターナショナルではありません
Association of Internet broadcaster it's
それはインターネット放送局の協会
clear worldwide what am I talking about
私は何を話しているのか
it's cat five dot TV / IA ib don't
それは猫の5つのドットTV / IAのibではない
forget as well check out our mobile
私たちのモバイルをチェックアウトするのも忘れて
website Doyle gonna have to get over
ウェブサイトDoyleが乗り越えなければならない
here so it doesn't find on face MDOT cat
ここでそれは顔で見つけられないので、MDOT cat
five dot TV scan that code or you can
5ドットテレビでそのコードをスキャンするか、できます
also burn on your idevice sir chrome on
またあなたの理想の教会の上のクロムを燃やす
your android device
あなたのアンドロイドデバイス
your browser thing on blackberry mk5 don
ブラックベリーmk5ドンのあなたのブラウザの事
t be big changes to our roku feed this
私たちのrokuフィードに 大きな 変化があります
week you know that last weekend had some
週末には先週末に
questions about the ability to watch the
時計を見る能力についての質問
live of course that's something that we
もちろん、それは私たちが
really are pushing toward with defensive
本当に守備に向かって進んでいる
devices an exceptional set-top box
優れたセットトップボックス
online so we've taken the liberty of
オンラインで私たちは自由の
making some big changes to the Roku feed
Rokuのフィードに大きな変更を加えました
if you're on a Roku device tonight
あなたが今夜ロクのデバイスを使っているなら
watching live please let us know in the
ライブを見て、私たちに知らせてください
chaplain category 53 notes directly
chaplainカテゴリ53のコメント
through our website let us know how the
私たちのウェブサイトを通じて、
quality is for the live feed now I
品質はライブフィード用です
understand that on-demand if you're
オンデマンドであれば理解する
watching
見ている
that live
ライブ
set of tests where / any pigs will
どのブタがどこでテストを行うかのテストセット
appreciate that very much so a topic
非常に多くのトピックに感謝
that is really tough to talk about a
それは本当に難しい話です
topic that is you know everybody we have
あなたは私たちが持っている 誰もが知っている話題
the sense of our own mortality and
私たち自身の死の感覚と
sometimes it's you know there comes a
時にはそれはあなたがそこに来ることを知っている
point in our lives where we really have
私たちの生活の中で私たちが本当に持っているポイント
to start thinking about you know what
あなたが何を知っているか考え 始める
should happen what will happen if I'm to
もし私がになると起こるはずのこと
leave this earth and while it's a topic
この地球を去り、それが話題である間に
that is rather sensitive so you know if
あなたが知っているので、それはかなり敏感です
you have young kids watching in the room
あなたは部屋で幼い子供たちを見ている
with you perhaps this is something you
おそらくこれはあなたと
know that they don't want to really
彼らは 本当にしたく ないことを知っている
think about mom and dad in this
お母さんとお父さんについて考える
particular scenario so it's a sensitive
特定のシナリオでは機密扱いです
topic but it's something that we do need
私たちが 必要とする もの です
to discuss when technology arrives that
技術がいつ到着するかを議論する
allows us to reach out to those that we
私たちが私たちに手を差し伸べることができます
love should something happen to us so
愛は何かが私たちに起こるはずです
Hilary Rumble is speaking with Kelly
ヒラリー・ランブルはケリーと話しています
lass alene from memories of me tonight
今夜私の記憶から老人のアレネ
and I'm gonna I'm going to sit back and
私は後ろに座るつもりです
let you ladies discuss this wonderful
あなたは女性がこの素晴らしい話を聞かせて
service that Kelly's introduced well
ケリーがうまく導入したサービス
hello viewers thank you for joining us
こんにちは視聴者は私たちに参加してくれてありがとう
we are here with Kelly lastly the
私たちはケリーと最後に
president of memories of me so memories
思い出の私の記憶の大統領
of me is an online service that provides
私のオンラインサービスは、
individuals with opportunity to to leave
離れる機会のある個人
behind messages and and special mementos
メッセージと特別な記念品の後ろに
for loved ones to receive after their
愛する人が彼らの後に受け取るために
passing so it is an uncomfortable
渡すと不快になります
subject for some of us and we want to be
私たちのいくつかのために被験者となりたい
sensitive to this but we're also
これに敏感ですが、
interested to hear more about memories
思い出をもっと知りたい
of me so Kelly can you tell us a little
私のことをケリーは少し教えてくれますか？
bit more about the service and what you
サービスの詳細とあなたの
do absolutely the whole idea actually I
絶対にすべてのアイデアを実際に行う
got started when my own father passed
私の父が過ぎた時に始まった
away during his eulogy I actually wrote
彼の追悼の間に私は実際に書いた
a dear dad letter to my father and I
私の父と私の親愛なるお父さんの手紙
talked about you know the different
あなたが 別のを 知っているの話
memories that we had and I started
私たちが持っていた思い出が始まった
wondering you know if my father had
私の父に
written a letter to me would he perhaps
私に手紙を書いたのはおそらく彼だろう
remind me of the time that we play golf
私たちがゴルフをする時間を思い出させる
and we got caught in a lightning storm
私たちは雷の嵐に巻き込まれた
would he tell me how he wanted me to
彼は私を望んでいた方法 を教えます
take care of my mother his wife of 45
私の母の45の彼の妻を世話をします
years or what he perhaps have a little
何年か彼はおそらく少し持っている
pearl of wisdom that he would like to
彼がしたいと知恵の真珠
share so that's sort of how the idea was
シェアそれはアイデアがあったかのようなものですので、
born and I thought you know this is an
生まれたと私はあなたがこれが知っていると思った
opportunity that people before they
彼らの前に人々がいる機会
passed they can store messages like that
渡された彼らはそのようなメッセージを保存できます
so just imagine for a moment if you come
あなた が来 たらちょっと想像してみてください
home from maybe your mother of
あなたの母親からの家
father's funeral you know should they
あなたが知っている父の葬儀
pass someday unfortunately but getting
残念ながら残念ながら
home and maybe a week later you receive
家に帰ってから1週間後に
this joyful message from a parent or a
親からのこの楽しいメッセージ、または
family member or loved one just how
家族や愛する人
uplifting and and how warm it would feel
爽快感とそれがどのように暖かく感じるか
to hear from than just one last time
最後の1 回だけから聞く
that would be very special what a neat
それ はとても素敵なものなのでしょうか？
idea and a unique and unique service
アイデアとユニークでユニークなサービス
I've never heard of anything like this
私は この ような ことは聞いたことがない
before how does this the service
どのようにこれはサービスの前に
actually work how do these one go about
実際にどのようにこれらの1つが行くか作業
getting connected with you it's actually
実際にあなたとつながっている
very easy you log on to the website
あなた はウェブサイト に簡単 にログオン でき ます
memories of me CA and you can register
私の思い出CAとあなたが登録することができます
for free it only takes a few minutes you
無料で数分しかかかりません
register a username and a password and
ユーザー名とパスワードを登録し、
you can type out the message that you
あなたはあなたにメッセージを打ち込むことができます
want to share with the recipients so you
受信者と共有したいので
actually start a letter each letter you
実際にあなたの手紙を始める
can send off to five recipients that one
5人の受信者に1人を送信することができます
letter and you can also upload a photo
写真をアップロードすることもできます
that you'd like to send with it okay
あなたは 大丈夫 、それを送りたいこと
well that seems very easy i actually did
よく私は実際にやったことは非常に簡単に思える
try making account and it took like two
アカウントを作ろうとすると2つのようになりました
seconds so yeah it's very user-friendly
秒だからそれは非常にユーザーフレンドリーです
excellent that way so why would people
そのように優れているので、なぜ人々が
perhaps use a service like memories of
おそらく記憶のようなサービスを使用する
me versus hand writing a letter and
私は手紙と手紙を書いて
hiding it in the drawer of their desk
机の引き出しに隠す
that sort of thing but that's a great
そのようなものだけど、それは素晴らしい
question and actually I've heard of
質問と実際に私が聞いたことがある
story after story of people who do have
物語の後の物語
a handwritten letter but people move
手書きの手紙ですが人々は 動いています
letters get forgotten houses
手紙は忘れられた家を得る
unfortunately burned down or they
残念ながら燃え尽きる
succumb to accidents and the letter can
事故に屈して 、手紙が缶に入る
be lost I also checked in the idea of
私はまたアイデアをチェックして失われる
maybe a safety deposit box because you
おそらくセーフティボックスです
could always put your letter or your
あなたの手紙やあなたの
items into a safety deposit box but even
安全預金箱に入れる
a safety deposit box I mean they charge
私は彼らが充電を意味するセーフティボックス
a monthly fee if you use the example of
月額料金はあなたの 例を使用している場合
a 30 year old who plans on being around
周りにいることを計画している30歳の
to the age 100 then you have 70 more
あなたは70歳以上に
years x 12 months a year which adds up
年x 12ヶ月/年
to thousands and thousands of dollars so
数千から数千ドルに
they were very vile viable and actually
彼らは非常に卑劣で実行可能であった
a very cheap alternative for people who
人々のための非常に安い選択肢
want to send their their their final
彼らの決勝戦を送る
thoughts and memories
思考と記憶
interesting so you mentioned before that
あなたがその前に述べたように面白い
people can send one letter up to five
人々は1つの手紙を5つまで送ることができます
people is there an option to write
人々は書くオプションがあります
multiple letters absolutely absolutely
複数の文字を絶対に絶対に
you can buy as many letters as you like
あなたは好きなだけ多くの手紙を購入することができます
really the first letter that you
本当に最初の手紙
purchase is a hundred dollars and you
購入は百ドルで、あなたは
can send it up to five recipients each
それぞれ5人の受信者に送信できます
additional letter that you purchase is
あなたが購入した追加の文字は
ten dollars ness so your first letter is
あなたの最初の手紙は 10ドルです
a hundred dollars your second letters
百ドルあなたの第二の手紙
ninety dollars and your third letter is
90ドル、あなたの3番目の手紙は
eighty dollars and so on okay so maybe I
80ドルなど大丈夫です
send one letter and I want to send it to
1通の手紙を送って送ってください
my five closest friends that might be my
私のかもしれない私の5人の親しい友人
first letter on my second letter I have
私の2番目の手紙の最初の手紙
four children so I might purchased a
私が 購入した かもしれないので、 4 人の子供
second letter and send it off to just my
二番目の手紙と私にそれを送信する
four children right because quite often
4人の子供は非常に頻繁に
the letter that you sent to your friends
あなたの友人に送った手紙
will differ from the letter that you
あなたの手紙とは異なるでしょう
send to your children or your sure yeah
あなたの子供やあなたの確かなええに送る
for sure the content would differ for
コンテンツが異なるのは確かです
each relationship you've had up to
あなたが持っていたそれぞれの関係
silver the lifetime so yeah that's a
一生のシルバーなので、 そう です
cool and every letter that you write you
クールであなたを書くすべての文字
have the option to upload a photo and
写真をアップロードするオプションがあります
send it off to those recipients as well
それらの受信者にも 送信してください
okay so how do you ensure that people
大丈夫ですか
receive the letters and how do you I
手紙を受け取って、どうすればいいですか？
guess verify that someone has indeed
誰かが本当にいることを確認する
passed and it is time to send the letter
渡され、手紙を送る時間です
absolutely well that's a great question
絶対にそれは大きな質問です
built into the website is a notifier
ウェブサイトに組み込まれているのは通知者です
system so when you have an account with
システムなので、あなたはアカウントを持っている
memories of me you will ask somebody to
私の思い出は、誰かに
notify us of your death so the easiest
あなたの死を私たちに知らせるのが一番簡単です
people to notify or have notify is you
あなたに知らせる、または通知する人々はあなたです
know a good friend of yours you can also
あなたの良い友達を知っていることもできます
have your lawyer who does your will or
弁護士にあなたの意志をしてもらうか
your pee away you can slip a little
あなたのおしっこは 、少し スリップ する ことができます
notice into that file ask them to keep
そのファイルへの通知は、
it there and then when they open up that
そこにそれは 彼らがいることを開く とき
file to distribute your estate they see
あなたの財産を配布するためのファイル
the letter and they'll notify us are
手紙と彼らが私たちに通知するでしょう
also fear the sort of individual who
また、個人の種類を恐れる
free plans their funeral you can lead
無料で葬儀を計画する
the letter with your a good funeral part
あなたの良い葬儀の部分と手紙
with your funeral and they will notify
あなたの葬儀で彼らは告げるでしょう
us that you passed we recommend that you
あなたが合格した私たちはあなたに
have at least two people to notify us
私たちに通知する少なくとも2人の人がいる
just so we can be sure right now we'll
ちょうど今 私達は 今 確信できる
verify that you have in fact passed by
あなたが実際に通過したことを確認してください
calling the funeral home where your
葬儀場に電話する
arrangements are being done or checking
手配中またはチェック中
with the newspaper and once you're deaf
新聞と一度あなたは ろう者 です
notice has been published we know it's
通知が公開されています
safe to to release the messages so in
メッセージをリリースするのに安全です
the event of say like a nun time
例えば修道女のようなイベント
death you weren't anticipating hopefully
あなたはうまくいくと予想していなかった
family members would be able to access
家族が アクセス する ことができるだろう
that individuals email to see that
その 個人の電子メールで
they've registered or if they hadn't
彼らは登録しているか、登録していない場合
made the arrangements prior like to let
事前に準備をしてみましょう
the right channels know I suppose
私が推測する正しいチャネル
absolutely well the the bottom line it
絶対に結論それは最終的にそれ
is important if you decide to utilize
あなたが利用することを決定した場合は重要です
memories of me that you have somebody to
あなたの誰かがいるという私の思い出
notify us and we can make sure that your
私たちに通知し 、 あなたの
messages get safely off to their
メッセージはそのメッセージに安全に
recipients very wise and just to rewind
受信者は非常に賢明で巻き戻すだけです
a little bit how long have you been
どのくらいあなたがいたのですか？
doing this for well I actually started
よくこれをやって、私は実際に始めた
about a year ago I had the idea i did
約1年前に私は私がしたアイデアを持っていた
some brainstorming i had a few focus
いくつかのブレーンストーミングにはいくつかの焦点があった
groups with different people in the
異なる人と
community that might want to use the
コミュニティを使用したいと考えるコミュニティ
service also with some complementary
いくつかの補完的なサービス
businesses such as funeral homes and
葬儀場や
senior services and just just to see
シニアサービスだけで見て
what they're feeling what their feedback
彼らが何を感じているのかフィードバック
was it was all all very positive because
すべてがとてもポジティブだったのは、
it's quite a unique service that hasn't
それはない非常にユニークなサービスです
really been done it's very any guy I
本当にそれは非常に任意の男だ完了
know I have never heard of anything like
私は何も聞いたことがないことを知っている
this before we're actually talking with
これは実際に話す前に
Kelly laughs Celine from memories of me
ケリーは私の思い出からセリーヌを笑う
an online service like a digital catan
デジタルカタンのようなオンラインサービス
capsule to send messages to your loved
あなたの愛する人にメッセージを送るカプセル
ones after their passing so if you want
あなたが欲しいなら、渡された後のもの
to check out her website in particular
特に彼女のウェブサイトをチェックする
its memories of me ta but you can check
その私の記憶は、あなたが確認することができます
out our site cat5 TV / mom m om memories
私たちのサイトを抜け出すcat5 TV / mom m om memories
of me and that can direct you as well if
もしあなたが私の
you're interested in checking it out and
あなたはそれをチェックアウトすることに興味があります
having a peek it's a very user friendly
それは非常にユーザーフレンドリーなピークを持っている
site i have checked it out myself i
サイト私はそれを自分でチェックアウトしている
signed up very easy very cool unique
非常に簡単に非常にクールなユニークなサインアップ
idea so i have a question some of us
アイデアだから私には いくつか 質問が ある
were watching are fairly tech savvy
かなり技術に精通している見ていた
users what would you suggest for those
あなたはそれらのために何を提案しますか？
who are not so internet savvy leg say my
インターネットに精通していない人は私のことを言う
grandma or grandpa that's our thing um
おばあちゃん、おばあちゃん、それは私たちのことです
how should they proceed maybe working
彼らはどのように作業を進めるべきか
with a loved one who's more cop so how
愛する人ともっと警官がいるので
do they could maybe if they know
彼らはおそらく彼らが知っているか
somebody else who is also set up an
また、設定されている他の誰か
account with memories of me they can get
彼らが得ることができる私の思いを説明
their assistant I know I'm pretty
彼らのアシスタント私 はかなり わかっ ている
tech-savvy myself but if I need some
ハイテクに精通していますが、
help I always go to my daughter who is
私はいつも私の娘に行くのを助けます
it to nature that's always an option
それは常にオプションです自然に
if you have any questions right on the
あなたに質問がある場合は、
site there's a contact us form all
サイトにはすべて私たちに連絡があります
perfect and there's also a 1-800 number
完璧で、1-800番もあります
so we beat we'd be happy to help with
だから我々は我々 が助けて幸せになるだろう打ちます
any questions or concerns you have yeah
あなたが持っている質問や懸念
so when a letter is these letters are
そうすれば、これらの文字は
typed these are not handwritten and
これらは手書きではありません。
scanned they're like a tight email your
スキャンされたものは、きついメールのようです
database stores thumb and then sends
データベースは親指を格納してから送信します
them out via email or prints them and
電子メールでそれらを出すか、それらを印刷します
send it as a letterer yeah how does that
それはlettererええとしてそれを送信する方法
work yes once we are notified of
私たちに通知されたらはいを働かせます
somebody's death we would of course
私たちはもちろん誰かの死
verify it before we send any emails out
メールを送信する前に確認してください
and it would be sent out via email and
それは電子メールで送信され ます
yeah as I'm sitting here I can imagine
私がここに座っているように、私は想像することができます
you know somebody at their computing
あなたは コンピューティングで 誰かを知っている
there might be just a little bit
ちょっとだけかもしれない
startled to see that all of a sudden
突然のことを見て驚いた
they open up their email so in fact
彼らは実際に自分の電子メールを開くので
there would be a little bit of a caveat
ちょっとした警告があります
so if you open up your email after
あなたがあなたのメールを開いたら
somebody passed you would get a message
誰かがあなたを渡してメッセージを受け取った
that states you have a letter for you
あなたにあなたの手紙があります
from memories of me and there'd be an
私の思い出から、
opportunity for them to click on a
それらをクリックする機会
button to see it so they have a moment
ボタンを押すと表示されます
to think about you know who's who's this
あなたが誰であるかを知ることを考える
loved one that's passed do I want to see
私は見たいものを愛しています
this or not no that's a good um that's a
良いUMことだだこのかなし
really good idea because that would be
それは本当に良い考えです
potentially very shocking to receive it
潜在的にそれを受け取るために非常にショッキングな
you know it could be here so that the
あなたはそれがここにあることを知っているので、
email reads from memories of me
電子メールは私の思い出から読み込みます
initially and then the option to open it
最初にそれを開くオプション
hmm actually you know what in my my
うーん、実際にあなたは私の私の中で何を知っている
chats it it was suggested to me another
それは私に別のものが示唆されたチャット
really good use for the letters is for
手紙のための本当に良い使用はです
information when my father passed away
私の父が亡くなった時の情報
it would have been nice if I had
私が持っていればそれは いいだろう
received a letter from him but now I
彼から手紙を受け取りましたが、今私は
only have one surviving suppose of
生存しているのは
course my mother and it was recently
私の母とコースは最近でした
suggested to me that that would be a
それは私に
great way for them to disseminate
彼らが普及するための素晴らしい方法
information the average internet user
平均インターネットユーザーの情報
has what 20 or 30 different usernames
20または30の異なるユーザー名
and passwords so that's a sort of things
とパスワードのようなものです
that you could include in a ladder my
あなたは 私 の はしごに私を 含めることができた
mother for her part I don't even know
彼女の一部のための母私は知らない
what bangs she bangs fence so it's a
彼女はフェンスを強打するので、それは
great opportunity for her to tell me
彼女が私に教える素晴らしい機会
which bank she's with maybe what her
彼女はおそらく彼女と一緒にいる銀行
account number is her passwords maybe
アカウント番号は彼女のパスワードかもしれない
she could tell me the name and telephone
彼女は私に名前と電話を教えることができた
of her account and there's there's no
彼女のアカウントには
end of information that she could share
彼女が共有できる情報の終わり
with us like me and my sister of course
私と私の姉妹のような私たちともちろん
her other daughter
彼女の他の娘
after she's passed let's another useful
彼女が通過した後に、もう1つ役立つ
letter that could be written that's
書かれているかもしれない手紙
actually a good idea but one thing that
実際には良い考えですが、
comes up to me is is in terms of like
私に似ているのは、
security so like if someone is saying
誰かが言っているようにセキュリティー
all this personal information how like
このすべての個人情報はどのように
do you ever see a letter like you just
あなたのような手紙を見たことがありますか？
see a file that comes to you you would
あなたに来るファイルを見てください
never see the content well actually
実際にはコンテンツを実際には見ない
there is uh there is a rather lengthy
かなり長い
terms of use and service and in a
利用規約とサービス、および
nutshell you have to be 18 years old or
あなたは18歳以上でなければなりません
older to use the service and you cannot
サービスを使用するには年をとっておらず、
say anything that is harmful or
有害なものや
malicious and constant content so there
悪意のあるコンテンツと不変のコンテンツ
is a point where we would go through the
我々が通過するだろう点です
information and make sure that there's
情報を 確認し て
nothing malicious before we sent the
私たちが送信する前に悪意がない
documents out okay and then in terms of
ドキュメントは大丈夫、 そして
storage because I know some of our
私はいくつかの
techie friends are probably wondering
techieの友人は おそらく疑問に思います
like could i hack could people hack into
私がハックすると、人々がハックする可能性があります
your site people like the tech aspect of
あなたのサイトの人々は、
the storage of that information well I'm
その情報の記憶はよく私は
going to try and do my IT providers and
私のITプロバイダと
justice here and trying to explain it in
ここで正義とそれを説明しようとする
my non tech version as best as possible
私のノンテクニカルバージョンは可能な限り最高です
but we have an ssl certificate it is a
私たちはSSL証明書を持っています
secure website and I know that he worked
私は彼が働いたことを知っている
very very hard to make sure that the the
こと を確認するために非常に非常に難しいです
password I think I'm saying this right
パスワード私はこの権利を言っていると思う
that it changes it sort of morphs every
それはそれを変えている
time somebody logs in so it cannot be
誰かがログインするとき
hacked into it's virtually it's
ハックしたのは事実だ
impossible to hack into there you go
あなたがそこに侵入することは不可能
that's I know you're all wondering this
それは私が知っているあなたがすべてこれを疑問に思っている
is sensitive information and not even
機密情報であり、
just like you know bank account or
銀行口座を知っているかのように
whatever potentially but like heartfelt
潜在的にでも心のこもったように
things and you wouldn't want people to
あなたは人々に
compromise that so absolutely can i
絶対にそうすることができる妥協
interject erinc over here addy at the
ここでは、
other guy again the the reason I want to
もう一度私がしたい 理由
interject is because I am a little bit
私が少ししているからです
more technically knowledgeable about
より技術的に知識が豊富
this kind of thing and I had the
この種のものと私は
opportunity well when when Hilary signed
ヒラリーが署名したときの機会
up for the service I was given the
私が与えられたサービスのために
opportunity to actually see the content
実際にコンテンツを見る機会
of the transaction as far as the
取引の
database and goes and what memories of
データベースとの
me is using is a cryptographically sound
私は暗号を使用しています
algorithm that is based on each
それぞれに基づいたアルゴリズム
individual user's account so
個々のユーザーのアカウント
the way I understand it is that for
私がそれを理解する方法は、
example if somebody were able to
誰かが
compromise your your account by say
あなたのアカウントを侵害する
knowing your password that password
あなたのパスワードを知っているパスワード
cannot be used to access anything else
他にアクセスするために使用することはできません
within the system so what that means
システム内で、その意味
from a hacker standpoint if I may
ハッカーの立場から、もし私が
interject is that if a hacker were to
interjectは、ハッカーが
compromise their database they would not
データベースを妥協しないでください
be able to decrypt any of the
の いずれかを解読 できる ようにする
information that is stored
格納されている情報
cryptographically in the database
データベース内で暗号的に
because they don't have the decryption
彼らは解読を 持っていないので
keys I didn't get to see all that but
キー私はすべてを見ることができませんでしたが、
there are multiple decryption keys one
1つに複数の復号鍵があります
of which is specific to the user account
ユーザーアカウントに固有のものです
whose data is being encrypted so from
そのデータはから暗号化されています
what I could see it's very well thought
私はそれが非常によく考えていることを見ることができた
out and probably better than most banks
おそらくほとんどの銀行よりも優れている
and certainly sony pictures so many
確かにソニーの写真は非常に多く
pictures could learn a couple of things
写真は、物事のカップルを学ぶことができました
from you guys that's all I have to say
皆さんから、私が言わなければならないのはそれだけです
well there you go Thank You Robbie for
あなたにはありがとう、あなたはRobbieのために行く
clarifying that because I know people
私が人々を知っているので
are now we're always hyper sensitive and
今私たちは常にハイパーセンシティブで、
aware of things that could go wrong so
間違っている可能性があることを認識している
anyways that is good news you guys are
とにかく皆さんには良いニュースです
good to go very secure site that's
非常に安全なサイトに行くのは良い
wonderful i'm glad to hear that i have
素晴らしい私は 私が持って いることを聞いてうれしい
another question actually i noticed on
実際に私が気づいた別の質問
your site you have three local charities
あなたのサイトには3つのローカルチャリティがあります
listed with the option of the user to
ユーザーのオプションで一覧表示されます
donate i forgot you said five percent
私が あなたに5％
five percent of the proceeds of the sale
売却代金の5％
to that particular charity yes which i
その特定の慈善団体へ
think is a really cool idea i was just
私はちょうどいいアイデアだと思う
wondering potentially in the future is
潜在的に将来的には不思議です
there way for other charities to try to
他の慈善団体に
opt-in to your service and absolutely
あなたのサービスへのオプトインと絶対に
yet no memories of me wants to be a good
まだ私の思い出は良いものになりたくない
corporate citizen so we do believe in
私たちが信じる企業市民
giving back to those charities for which
それらの慈善団体に還元する
perhaps somebody's passed from i believe
おそらく誰かが私から信じられなくなった
the charities include the Breast Cancer
慈善団体には、乳がん
Society of Canada Alzheimer's and
カナダアルツハイマー病協会
there's one more Gilda Gilda thought
Gilda Gildaの考えがもう1つあります
that's correct thank you the hospice
それは正しいホスピスに感謝します。
care if there are other charities that
他の慈善団体がある場合は注意してください
would like to be recognized on our
私たちに認識されたい
website we'd be happy to post their logo
私たちはロゴを掲示することができます
and have a percentage of the proceeds go
収入の一定割合を持っている
to their charity because I mean we we
彼らの慈善団体 に
want to be good corporate citizens and
良き企業市民になりたい
we would like to help stamp out some of
私たちはいくつかの
these awful diseases that lead to some
これらにつながる恐ろしい病気
people's death
人々の死
great idea I I think that's an excellent
素晴らしいアイデアは、それが優れていると思います
idea Thank You Larry are there any other
アイデアはありがとうございます。
tidbits you think people should know
人々 が知っておくべきだと思うあなた
about your site on why choose you over
なぜあなたを選択するかについてのあなたのサイトについて
it why again it's like a unique service
それは再びユニークな サービスのようなもの です
I've never heard of anything like this
私はこのようなことは聞いたことがない
before um to have any last minute
最後の1分はum前に
thoughts you want to throw out there Oh
あなたはああ そこに投げたい思考
wha thank you for that I I think if you
あなた に 感謝しています。私 はあなたが
look at this standpoint from cost alone
費用のみからこの観点を見てください
if your cost minded you should know that
あなたの費用が気になるなら、 それを知るべきです
a safety deposit box over the course of
安全な預金箱
well if I'm a 30-year old and I want to
もし私が30歳で、私はしたい
live to 100 another seven years of a
の 100別の7歳まで生きます
safety deposit box is going to cost me a
セーフティボックスが私にかかる費用 は
lot of money there are websites that a
たくさんのお金があるウェブサイトがあります
little bit similar to ours but a little
私たちと少し似ていますが少しです
more macabre maybe a nature that have
もっと恐ろしいかもしれない
tried it and they charge a subscription
それを試し、彼らはサブスクリプションを請求する
base and again 70 years of my life x 12
ベースと私の人生の 70年x 12
months a year that's 840 months times
840ヶ月の時間だヶ月〜1年
even as low as three dollars it's uh
たとえ3ドルもの低さであっても
it's a lot more than we are yeah so and
それは我々がそうであるよりもはるかに多い
we'll take care of you if you sign up
あなたがサインアップすれば、世話をします
with memories of me I would love for
私の思い出で私は大好きです
users if they do nothing else when they
ユーザーが他に何もしなければ
go on to the website if you would please
あなたがしたい場合は、ウェブサイトに行く
check out the slideshow and maybe you
スライドショーをチェックしてください
give you a flavor of the kind of joy and
あなたの喜びの種類の風味を与え、
happiness that we would like to to share
私たちが共有したい幸福
with your your family and friends yeah
あなたの家族と友達と一緒に ええ
Robbie just pulling up the website here
Robbieがここでウェブサイトをプルアップする
I just saw a little sneak peek of that
私はちょうど それ の 少しのスニーク ピークを 見ました
so yeah definitely check out their site
だから間違いなく自分のサイトをチェックアウトする
memories of me dot CA and you can find
私の思い出CAがあります
out more information by checking out
チェックアウトして詳細情報を表示する
cat5 TV / mom memories of me Thank You
私の CAT5 TV /ママの思い出は、 ありがとうございました
Kelly for joining us and for sharing bit
私たちに加わり、ビットを共有するためのケリー
of your passion and a great idea for us
あなたの情熱と私たちの素晴らしいアイデアの
to explore thank you for so much for
探検するためにあなたのためにありがとう
having me back to you Robbie thanks for
あなたに戻ってきてくれたロビー
me thanks Kelly this is category 5
私に感謝ケリーこれはカテゴリ5です
technology TV and thank you for joining
技術テレビと参加していただきありがとうございます
us tonight triple w category 5 TV hey
私たち今夜トリプルwカテゴリ5テレビねえ
we've got lots of viewer questions that
視聴者からの質問がたくさんあります
are over here waiting for Hillary we're
ここでヒラリーが待っている
going to go through the mail bag in just
ただのメールバッグを通過 しようとして
a couple minutes time but as Hillary
数分の時間が、しかしヒラリーとして
makes her way back to the the studio
スタジオに戻ります
desk we're going to throw over to to
私たちが捨てようとしている机
Sasha who is in Jamaica tonight hey
今夜はジャマイカにいるサシャ
Sasha it's Tuesday january twentieth
サシャそれは火曜日の1月20日です
2015 and here are the stories were
2015年には
covering this
これを覆う
week the german city of munich wants to
週 ミュンヘン のドイツの都市が 欲しい
help shape the future of libre office so
自由な事務所の将来を形作るのに役立つ
they've joins the document foundation
彼らは文書基盤に加わりました
advisory board the mint box mini has
マインドボックスミニが持っている諮問委員会
double the performance of its
その性能を倍増させる
predecessor and will fit in your pocket
前任者とあなたのポケットに収まる
goodbye Google glass we barely knew you
さようなら私たちがかろうじてあなたを知っていたグラス
imagine being able to generate power by
パワーを生成できると想像してください
walking that's what's being developed by
歩くことは、
a team of German researchers who plan to
ドイツの研究者チームが
use the technology to power self-lacing
この技術を使用して自己彫刻を強化する
shoes target is closing all its Canadian
靴のターゲットはカナダ全土を閉鎖しています
stores not even two years after moving
移動後 2 年 も 経って いない店舗
here Canadian auntie's anti-spam laws
ここカナダの叔母の反スパム法
have made it illegal for programs to
プログラムでは
auto-update without your consent and the
あなたの同意なしに自動更新
british-built Mars rovers sent to mars
火星に送られた英国の火星探査機
in search of signs of alien life was set
外国人の生活の兆しを求めて
to land and never heard from again now
着陸し、今からもう一度聞いたことがない
eleven years later NASA's got eyes on
11年後に NASAが目を引く
its whereabouts these stories are coming
彼らの所在地は、これらの物語が来ている
right up don't go anywhere introducing
右上がりはどこにも行かない
Beltone first a revolutionary new
ベルトン初の革新的な新しい
hearing aid so small you can hardly see
あなたがほとんど見ることができないほど小さい補聴器
it so comfortable you can hardly feel it
それはあなた がそれをほとんど感じることができないのでとても快適です
for the first time ever you can control
あなたが初めて制御することができます
hearing aids directly from your iPhone
あなたのiPhoneから直接補聴器
pick up the phone listen to music and
電話を拾うと音楽を聴く
use your hearing aids like wireless
ワイヤレスのような補聴器を使用する
headphones hear everything that matters
ヘッドフォンが重要なことをすべて聞く
try Beltone first for a free trial call
Beltoneを最初に試してみてください
one eight hundred Bell tone now
1つの850のベル音色
i'm sascha through madison here the top
私はここでマディソンを通してサッシャですトップ
stories from the category 5 TV news room
カテゴリ5テレビニュースルームからのストーリー
the city of Munich has joined the
ミュンヘン市は
document foundation advisory board
文書基盤アドバイザリーボード
Germany's third-largest city has a long
ドイツで3番目に大きい 都市は長い
history of using open source software
オープンソースソフトウェアの使用履歴
much of it well documented more than
それの多くは、
16,000 pcs of public employees run the
16,000人の公務員が
open source linux linux operating system
オープンソースのfreshmeat_linux / Linux]のLinuxオペレーティングシステム
and the city makes heavy use of Libre
そしてこの都市はリブーを大いに活用しています
Office and it's open file formats the
Officeとそれが開いているファイル形式です
role of the advisory board is to provide
諮問委員会の役割は、
the document foundation with feedback
フィードバックを持つ文書基盤
feedback on how the software is being
ソフトウェアがされている方法についてのフィードバック
used what features or improvements need
どの機能や改善が必要かを使用
to be made providing assistance and
支援を提供するように
initiatives community projects and
イニシアチブコミュニティプロジェクト
marketing and providing donations to
マーケティングと寄付の提供
further development and outreach
さらなる開発とアウトリーチ
companies pay an annual fee is a member
企業は年会費を支払うメンバーです
of the board the exact cost of which
ボードの正確なコスト
varies depending on contribution in the
寄付によって異なります
number of employees with fees starting
手数料を開始する従業員の数
at five thousand dollars and topping out
5000ドルでトッピング
at twenty thousand dollars as a heavy
重くて2万ドルで
user of the LibreOffice productivity
LibreOfficeの生産性のユーザー
suite the city of munich's contributions
ミュンヘンの貢献都市
will be invaluable in helping to guide
ガイドに役立つ上で非常に貴重なものとなるでしょう
the project towards even greater
さらに大きな方向へのプロジェクト
usability that is great news Robbie my
有用性は素晴らしいニュースです。Robbie my
goodness who knows what it'll bring yeah
それはそう持っていきますかを知っている善
we'll see we'll see good Linux
私たちは良いLinuxを見るだろう
awesomeness no more Linux awesome
もうawesomeness Linuxは素晴らしい
awesomeness Linux Mint has announced
Linux Mintが発表した驚異
that a new pc in its mint box line of
そのミントボックスラインの新しいpcを
pcs is coming to in the spring the mint
春にミントにPCが来ています
box mini the new box continues the
新しい箱はミニを続けます
distros long-standing partnership with
長年のパートナーシップとのディストリビューション
israeli computer manufacturer compu lab
イスラエルのコンピュータメーカーcompu lab
which began with the release of the
それは
original mint box pc back in 2012 that
2012年に元のミントボックスのPCに戻る
was followed the year after by the more
1年後に は
powerful mint box to a device which sold
強力なミントボックスを販売したデバイスに
out in Europe on its Amazon debut last
ヨーロッパでは Amazonのデビューで最後に
year the mint box mini is five times
年ミントボックスミニは5回です
smaller than the original mint box and
元のミントボックスより小さく
is barely an inch tall like the previous
以前のようにわずかに1インチの高さです
editions the new model is fanless with
新しいモデルはファンレスです
the case design working as a passive
パッシブとして機能するケースデザイン
cooling system previous mid box models
冷却システム前のミッドボックスモデル
had a very distinctive look but if we
非常に独特の外観を持っていたが、我々の場合
can be critical of anything with the
何があっても
mint box mini it
ミントボックスミニ
utilitarian design it looks like a
実用的なデザインは、
little dsl modem wearing and aluminum
小さなdslモデムとアルミニウムを着用
shed that said something this time he is
今度は彼が何かを言った小屋
going to be easy to hide away if you
あなたがいれば隠れるのは簡単だろう
want the mint box mini offers twice the
ミントボックスのミニが2回提供したい
performance of the mint box to in a form
フォームのミントボックスのパフォーマンス
factor you could slip into a pocket
あなたがポケットに入れることができる要因
inside it out and am da for 6,400 tcp
その中には6,400 tcp
you which is a 1 gigahertz 64-bit and
あなたは 1ギガヘルツの 64ビットと
boasts four cores it also has a radio on
4つのコアを備えています。
our 3gp you four gigabytes ram and a
私たちの3gpあなたは4ギガバイトのRAMと
senha 64 gigabytes solid state hard
senhaソリッドステートハード 64ギガバイト
drive that is a lot Robbie yeah I'll say
ドライブはそれほどですロビーええ、私は言うでしょう
I could make a nice little web server if
私は素敵な小さなWebサーバーを作ることができます
you ask me with those kind of specs you
あなたはそのような種類のスペックで私に尋ねる
could host a website on that would be
その上にウェブサイトをホストすることができます
screaming fast let alone what else you
早く叫んで他に何を
could do with it as a desktop but yeah I
デスクトップと同じようにすることができますが、私はええ
slipping into your pocket I just love
あなたのポケットに入って私はただ愛する
how absolutely tiny it is and that don't
それがいかに絶対的に小さいか、 それ はない
use a lot of power to write you think
あなたが考えることを書くために多くの力を使う
about the fact that this thing you think
あなたが思うこの事実について
I I think in terms of web servers and
私はWebサーバーと
things like that and services and but
そのようなものやサービスなど
the amount of power that a full-size
フルサイズの電力量
server uses versus a little solid-state
サーバーの使用量と少しのソリッドステート
device with not even a moving part yeah
可動部分でもない装置
how how excellent and then one of the
どのようにどのように優れた、その後の 1
problems with servers is if they
サーバーの問題は、
overheat right so if it's that small
それが小さければ右に過熱する
it's got to be easy to keep cool you
それはあなたを涼しく保つことが容易でなければならない
would passive it's aluminum so it's like
受動的なのはアルミニウムだから似ている
a heat sink right so that what's a
ヒートシンクは右のように
comparison I guess if you've seen the
私はあなたが
inside of a computer you've seen a heat
あなたが熱を見たことがあるコンピュータの内部
sink but like chips will have like an
シンクだけどチップのように
aluminum fin on it that draws the heat
熱を引き出すアルミフィン
away from the chip right yeah so the
チップから離れて右のええそう
whole computer is based on that kind of
コンピュータ全体はそのような種類の
passive cooling system yeah looks pretty
受動的な冷却システムええはかなり見える
good that is awesome the mint box mini
ミントボックスミニの素晴らしいです
will be 295 dollars when sold to the US
米国への販売時には295ドルになります
and 295 pounds shipped in Europe not bad
ヨーロッパで出荷された295ポンドは悪くない
a portion of the sales will go to
販売の一部は
supporting linux mint and cover the cost
Linuxミントをサポートし、コストをカバーする
of the whopping five year warranty since
以来5年間の無償保証の
these are gonna be sold five years Wow
これらは5年間売られるだろううわー
five years whopping five years these are
これらの5年間は
gonna be sold on Amazon we should add
私たちは追加する必要がAmazonで販売されるつもり
these to the shop category five dot TV
これらは店カテゴリ5ドットテレビに
so if you want one once they're
あなたが一度それを望むなら、彼らは
available why don't we do that that
利用可能な理由はありません
would be great maybe I could get one
多分私は1つを得ることができる素晴らしい ことです
over
以上
view it for my show area perfect little
私のショーエリアを完全に少し見てください
device for tribal yes Google is ending
Googleが終了される部族そうするためのデバイス
sales of its google glass eyewear the
Googleのグラスアイウェアの販売
company insists it is still committed to
会社はそれがまだ
launching the smart glasses as a
スマートメガネを
consumer product but it will stop
消費者製品が停止します
producing glass in its present form
ガラスを現在の形で生産する
instead it will focus on future versions
代わりに将来のバージョンに焦点を当てます
of glass with work carried out by
によって行われた仕事のガラスの
different divisions than before the
以前よりも別の部門
Explorer program which gave software
ソフトウェアを与えたExplorerプログラム
developers the chance to buy a glass for
開発者はガラスを購入するチャンス
fifteen hundred dollars or nine hundred
1500ドルまたは900ドル
ninety pounds will close the program was
90ポンドはプログラムを終了する
launched in the united states in 2013 it
2013年に米国で発売
was then opened up to anyone and was
誰にでも開かれていた
launched in the UK last summer it has
去年の夏にイギリスで発売された
been expected that it would be followed
それが続くと予想された
by a reasonably befall of reasonably
合理的に合理的に発生する
quickly by a full consumer launch but
完全なコンシューマー向けの発売ですぐに
from next week the search firm will stop
来週から検索会社が停止する
taking orders for the product but it
製品の注文を受け取りますが、
says it will continue to support
それが引き続きサポートすると言います
companies that are using glass the
ガラスを使用している企業は、
things learned from glass will be used
ガラスから学んだことが使用されます
in the development of
の 開発で
yet-to-be-announced future products from
まだ発表されていない未来の製品を
google several companies have launched
Googleはいくつかの企業が立ち上げた
smart glasses and various other forms of
スマートメガネ、その他の様々な形態
wearable technology but no single
ウェアラブルな技術だが、単一のものはない
product has yet proved to be a major hit
製品はまだ大きな打撃を受けています
that technology companies are looking
その技術企業は探している
for as they seek out the next big thing
彼らは次の 大きなもの を求めているから
google is tried to present this
Google はこれを 提示 しようとして います
announcement just as another step of the
発表のもう一つのステップとして
evolution of amazing innovation but make
驚くべきイノベーションの進化
no mistake Google glass is dead at least
間違いなくGoogleのガラスは少なくとも死んでいる
in its present form I'm not really upset
現在の形で私は本当に動揺していません
about this because I wasn't all that
私 はそのすべてではなかった ので 、 これ について
impressed by google glass truly honest
本当に正直なGoogleグラスに感銘を受けました
but if you had spent the money to buy
あなたが買うためにお金を費やしていたら
one thinking that it was going to evolve
それが進化すると考えていた人
into a more popular project mm-hmm and
より一般的なプロジェクトmm-hmmと
then it's basically dead i would like
それは基本的に私が望む死んでいる
wearable technology that put people
人々を置く着用可能な技術
around you at ease because people
あなたの周りに安心して
wearing Google glass or even people
Googleのガラスや人物を着て
wearing like a a watch that takes
腕時計のように身に着ける
pictures or video yeah makes me feel
写真やビデオのええ私は気分にさせる
really uncomfortable like as soon as I
私の ように すぐに 本当に不快な
see somebody with one of those watches
それらの時計の1つを持つ誰かを見なさい
on I think to myself oh you were
私はあなたがたああ 自分自身に考えます
recording this conversation right and I
この会話権と私を記録する
never had a conversation with somebody
誰かと 会話 したことがない
with Google glass on but i'm pretty sure
Googleのガラスでは、私はかなり確信している
that i would feel like they were you
彼らがあなたのように感じるだろう
know
知っている
recording me yeah I mean and it's kind
私を覚えている私は意味し、それは親切です
of one of those things it's like the
そのようなものの一つの
bluetooth headset it was a fad you've
Bluetoothヘッドセットはあなたがしていた流行だった
got to wear it but then you realize that
それを 着るようになった が、その後 、あなたはそれを実感
okay don't wear it all the time don't
大丈夫 、 それは すべての時間を 着用 しないでください
wear it all the time and Google glasses
いつも着て、Googleの 眼鏡
is no exception to that rule yeah yeah
そのルールの例外ではない
that's true i just i serve people that
それは本当です。
wear the bluetooth earpiece and i have a
ブルートゥースイヤホンを着て、私は持っている
really hard time when they're kind of
彼らが一種の
looking off knowing whether or not
それを知っているかどうかを見落とす
they're actually okay Julia can tell you
彼らは実際に大丈夫ですジュリアはあなたに伝えることができます
story i grasp it I was in the shopping
物語私はそれを把握私は ショッピングにいた
center and you know i'm i'm an outgoing
あなたは私が私が発信していることを知っています
guy and I don't mind you know conversing
男と私はあなた が会話 を 知って 気にしない
with strangers and stuff and this lady
見知らぬ人やものとこの女性
was walking by and she was talking
歩いていて彼女が話していた
awareness I said I'm sorry I didn't hear
私は聞いていないことを申し訳なく思った
you what did you say something like that
あなたは何のような こと を言ったのですか？
and she says oh this idiot just started
彼女はああ、このばかはちょうど始まったと言う
talking to me randomly just talking on
私と無作為に話すだけで話す
this bluetooth he's just walking around
このブルートゥスはちょうど歩いている
with a bluetooth headset yes like come
ブルートゥースヘッドセットがはいっているようにはい
on there was a commercial about that
それについての商業があった
about people in a grocery store having
食料品店の人々が持っていることについて
exactly that awkward interaction that
ちょうどその厄介な相互作用
happened to you actually it actually
実際にあなたに実際に起こった
happened to Robbie so this is why Google
Robbieに起こったので、これがGoogle
glass is like an ear hit but I'm a mess
ガラスは耳のようなものですが、私は混乱しています
so here's a great invention that I would
ここには私が
like as a waitress German researchers
ウェイトレスのようなドイツの研究者
have built shoe size devices that
靴サイズのデバイスを作りました
harvest power from the act of walking
歩く行為からの収穫力
the technology could be used to power
この技術を利用して電力を供給することができます
wearable electronic sensors without the
ウェアラブル電子センサー
need for batteries there are two
バッテリーの必要性は2つあります
separate devices a shock harvester that
ショックハーベスタ
generates power when the heel strikes
かかとが叩かれたときに発電する
the ground and a swing harvester that
地面とスイングハーベスタ
produces power when the foot is swinging
足が揺れているときに力を発する
both energy harvesting devices generate
両方のエネルギーハーベスティングデバイスは、
power by exploiting the motion between
間の動きを利用して
magnets and coils as the magnetic field
磁場としての磁石とコイル
of a moving magnet passes by the
移動する磁石の
stationary coil a voltage is induced and
固定コイルに電圧が誘起され、
an electric current is generated the
電流が生成される
energy they generate is still relatively
彼らが生成するエネルギーはまだ比較的です
small in the three to four milliwatt
3〜4ミリワットの小さい
range at their peak that's not nearly
ピークに達していない
enough to charge a smartphone for
スマートフォンを充電するのに十分な
example which would would typically
典型的には
require about 2,000 milliwatts but it is
約2,000ミリワットを必要とするが、それは
enough to power small sensors and
小さなセンサーに電力を供給するのに十分な
transmitters opening up a range of new
新しい範囲を開くトランスミッタ
applications so I wonder what sort of
アプリケーションので、私はどのような種類の
applications you could have on something
あなたが何かに持つことができるアプリケーション
that
それ
like small energy wise you couldn't
小さなエネルギーのようにあなたはできませんでした
charge a smartphone but maybe you could
スマートフォンを充電してください
monitor a heartbeat or something oh yeah
心拍や何かを監視する
maybe a like something like pacemakers
ペースメーカーのようなものかもしれない
or things that are you yeah monitoring
あなたが 監視しているもの
yes fitness exactly uh I use the word
はいフィットネスを正確に私は単語を使用する
stuff cuz I don't know the technical
私は技術的には分からない
term fitness stuff I don't you know
私はあなたが知っていない長期のフィットネスのもの
referral I don't know anything about
紹介私は何も知らない
fitness stuff come on but you know why I
フィットネスのものが来るが、なぜ私は知っている
at the cottage we've got a flashlight
コテージには懐中電灯があります
with one of those magnet with the coils
それらの磁石の1つにコイルが付いています
and you shake the flashlight and it
あなたは懐中電灯を振り、それを
charges the battery and then you turn it
バッテリーを充電してからそれを回します
on and you've got your flashlight you
あなたはあなたの懐中電灯を持っています
don't ever have to replace the batteries
電池を交換する必要はありません
on on the flashlight so it makes sense
懐中電灯の上でそれは意味をなさない
right you know what actually makes sense
実際 に理にかなっていることはわかっている
to be honest that in mind is if you had
正直言って、もしあなたが
like a little light on the bottom of
下の小さな光のように
these shoes that when you were creating
これらの靴は、あなたが作成していたときに
energy instead of having one of you know
あなたが知っているのではなく、エネルギー
joggers at night they have to wear all
彼らはすべてを着用する必要があります夜にジョギング
of those reflective doodads so if you
それらの反射的なdoodadsの
had like robots we say to the kids the
ロボットのように私たちは子供たちに
kids we joke that they your runner you
私たちは彼らが あなたのランナーであること を冗談を言う
look like a robot yeah and if you're
ええ、ロボットのように見える、 あなたがしている 場合
with like the kids old flashy shoes
子供のような古い派手な靴
right but if you had something that's
あなたが何かを持っていれば
sensed when it was dark then you know
それが暗かった時に感知した
you know alert any of those flashy shoes
あなたはそれらの派手な靴のいずれかに注意を知っている
though my kids have those flashy shoes
私の子供たちはその派手な靴を持っていますが
and once the batteries are dead their
一度バッテリーが消滅したら
garbage right as far as the flashing
ガーベッジは、点滅するまで
goes because two kids that's important
重要なのは2人の子供だから
so if it stops flashing it's no longer
それが点滅を止めるなら、もはやそれはありません
any good so something like this all of a
このような何か良いので、何かのすべて
sudden it is able to self charge right
突然それは自己の責任を負うことができる
how perfect is that so this is this is
それがどれくらい完璧なのか、これはこれです
the information this is what they're
情報これは彼らが何であるか
going to do with this new technology
この新技術と一緒に行く
clovis you leaf from h.s GI MIT a
あなたは hs GI MIT からの葉
research center in Germany said the
ドイツの研究センターは
swing harvester was developed with the
スイングハーベスターは、
intention of making a self-lacing shoe
自己靴を作る意図
for the elderly way to go Marty but yeah
高齢者のためにマーティを行くが、ええ
way to go the shoe would detect when a
靴を履く方法は
user stepped into it and lace itself up
ユーザーはそれに足を踏み入れ、それ自身をひも付けます
as well as open up again one required
また必要なものをもう一度開く
hopefully the harvesting device would
うまくいけば収穫装置は
generate the energy for the closing
閉鎖のためのエネルギーを生成する
mechanism details of the advanced are
上級者のメカニズムの詳細
outlined in the journal smart materials
ジャーナルスマートマテリアルで概説
and structures this is just really
これは本当に構造です
positive great use of new technology I
新しい技術を積極的に活用する
love it it's so simple I and it's
それはとてもシンプル だと私は それを愛する
something that we've been waiting for
私たちは待っていた何か
for some time from Back to the Future
バック・トゥ・ザ・フューチャー
self-lacing shoes and you
セルフレーシングシューズとあなた
oh that's lazy but no wait for the
ああ、それは怠惰だが、待つことはない
elderly the perfect or somebody was like
高齢者は完璧か誰かのようだった
a real bad like back you jack thinking
あなたの背中のような本当の悪い考えをジャック
yeah mobility issues in any way right so
どのような方法であれ、モビリティの問題はそう正しい
not just the elderly but even you know
高齢者だけでなく、あなたも知っている
ports injuries and stuff and stuff and
ポートの怪我とかとか と
stuff hey I know all about sports
私はスポーツについて知っている
injuries Oh meanwhile in canada two
一方でカナダ人2人の傷害
major retailers are calling it quits in
大手小売業者は、
canada target canada announced on
カナダは、
january fifteenth that it will close 133
1月15日は閉鎖される133
stores across Canada the US based
カナダ全土の店舗
retailer launched in Canada in March
3月にカナダで発売された小売業者
2013 too high expectations unfortunately
残念なことに 2013年の高い期待
due to numerous problems such as higher
高いなどの多くの問題のために
prices and less selection in Canada than
価格はカナダよりも少ない
the u.s. it never established itself in
私たちは決してそれ自体を確立しなかった
the Canadian market due to higher prices
より高い価格によるカナダ市場
and less stock yes you know what if I
在庫を減らしてください
can just say one of the problems that i
ちょうど私が
had with target coming into canada is
カナダに来る目標があった
that they bought Zellers which is a
彼らはZellersを購入した
chain that we grew up with and they shut
私たちは一緒に育った彼らは閉じたチェーン
them all down and people were out of
それらはすべてダウンし、人々 は
work so it really felt like the u.s.
本当に私たちのように感じた
coming in and shutting down our stores
私たちの店に入るとシャットダウン
so I don't think it's about stock and
だから私はそれ が株式についてだとは思わない
those kinds of things so much as boy
少年のようなもの
maybe an unspoken boycott of everyone
多分誰もが暗黙のボイコット
who loved the H like the Hudson's Bay
ハドソンズベイのようにHを愛した人
Company though right okay so here's a
会社は大丈夫だからここにいる
funny story about how passionate and
どのように情熱的な
patriotic I was young when I was younger
愛国者私が若い頃は若かった
so we had a fairly well-known American
私たちはかなり有名なアメリカ人でした
big-box store move into Barry and I
バリーと私のビッグボックスストアへの移動
boycotted it firm there for years or
それを数年前からボイコットした
maybe even five after it moved in and um
それは中に移動し、UM後多分5
I sort of similarly did the same thing
私も同様に同じことをしました
with target I thought to myself it's
ターゲットと私は自分自身にそれが思った
American I can just go down the street
アメリカン私はちょうど通りを降りることができます
and get all my stuff from and then I
以下と から、すべて私のものを取得し、I
realized that I have become so used to
私はとても慣れてきたことに気付きました。
shopping at Walmart that I've now turned
ウォルマートでショッピングして
it Canadian in my head sure and as the
それは私の頭の中で確かにカナダ人です。
donut don't get us wrong there's nothing
ドーナツは何も私たちに間違ってはいません
to do with America you know anything
あなたは何かを知っているアメリカとやりたい
like that it has to do with the business
それは ビジネスと関係し ているように
practice of Anna
アンナの練習
and companies and shutting them down
企業とその閉鎖
putting their people exactly like my
彼らの人々をまさに私のように置く
people who are close to me family and
私の家族に近い人と
friends who had worked with Zellers for
Zellersと仕事をしていた友人たち
so many years all of a sudden losing
何年もの間、突然失う
their work after after so many years of
長年の後の彼らの仕事
faithful service with the company yeah
会社との誠実なサービス
yeah absolutely it has nothing to do
ええ、絶対にそれは何もしていない
with the American companies it has to do
それがしなければならないアメリカ企業と
with you know losing the Canadian waters
あなたはカナダの海を失うことを知っている
yeah consequently the company lost about
そう、会社は
two billion dollars over two years the
2年間で20億ドル
closure meet the closures mean 18,000
クロージャーが18,000クロー
employees will lose their jobs many of
従業員は多くの
targets locations were formerly zeller
ターゲットの場所は以前はzellerでした
stores meanwhile sony canada also
店舗も一方ソニーカナダ
announced it will shut down all its
それがすべての
doors over the next six to eight weeks
次の6〜8週間のドア
it has 14 stores with three of them in
14店舗あり、3店舗あり
the lower mainland I'm surprised they're
下の本土私は彼らが驚いている
that small Johnny used to be a like the
小さなジョニーは以前は同じように
sony store was a big deal we may be in
ソニーストアは、我々がであってもよい大したことでした
the day it's true yeah I am i but I
本当の日私は私ですが、 私は私です
can't remember like I can't think of the
私は思うことができないように覚えていない
last time I was in a sony store which is
最後に私はソニーの店にいた
funny i guess they must have been paring
面白い 私は、彼らが ペアリング されている必要があります推測します
back slowly it's hard when you're when
あなたがいるときにゆっくりと戻ってくるのは難しい
you're a brand when you're a specific
あなたが特定のときにあなたはブランドです
brand if if like think of any brand and
もしあれば、どんなブランドを考えていても
say let's open a store that is specific
具体的な店舗を開きましょう
to that brand while it's a premium
それがプレミアムである間にそのブランドに
priced brand and everything you know you
あなたが知っているすべての値段のブランド
go to a big box store where there are 10
そこには10の大きな箱の店に行く
different brands to choose from and you
あなたとあなたから選ぶべき異なったブランド
can choose based on quality and price
品質 と価格に 基づいて選択できます
versus walking into a store where
どこの店に行くのか
everything is one brand and you have no
すべてが1つのブランドであり、あなたはない
say in the price or the selection the
価格や選択肢で言う
japan-based company has not released a
日本の会社は
statement explaining why the stores are
なぜ店舗があるのか​​を説明する声明
being closed the closures were announced
閉鎖された閉鎖は発表された
in the wake of the much-publicised Sony
多くの公表ソニー のきっかけに
Entertainment hack linked to the release
リリースにリンクした エンターテイメントの ハック
of the Vancouver shot film the interview
バンクーバーショット映画のインタビュー
hmm interesting all right so who knows
うーん、誰も知っているので、すべての権利が面白い
maybe the interview caused Sony did I
ソニーのインタビューで
don't know that there's actually any
実際に何か があることを知らない
relation with Sony Pictures yeah I don't
ソニーピクチャーズとの関係私はそうではありません
know all right this week in canada
今週は カナダで 大丈夫だと 知って いる
installing computer programs without
コンピュータプログラムをインストールせずに
consent we became a civil offense
私たちは 市民犯罪 になりまし た
punishable by fines under the new
新しい罰金に処罰される
regulations that form part of canada's
カナダの一部である規制
anti-spam legislation it is
スパム対策の法律
now illegal for a website to
のウェブサイトのために今違法
automatically install software on a
ソフトウェアを自動的に
visitor's computer or an app on your
訪問ユーザーのコンピュータまたはあなたのアプリ
phone with to be outdated without first
最初に電話をかけずに電話を切る
obtaining express consent from the owner
所有者から明示的同意を得る
or another authorized party hmm that's
または他の許可された当事者
good I think that's great yeah I mean
良いことだと思うよ
except that if you're going to be sort
あなたがソートするつもりならば
of malicious anyhow you're probably not
とにかくあなたはおそらく
going to listen to the rule that you
あなた のルール を聞くつもりです
ought not to be you know you're not I'm
あなたが私ではないことを知ってはいけないはずです
saying like but I suppose if there are
好きだと言いますが、もしあれば
fines in the hope is that they're going
希望の罰金は彼らが行くことです
to be able to crack down on it but how
それを打ち破ることができるが、どのように
many of these websites that are
これらのウェブサイトの多くは
distributing software which is going to
予定されているソフトウェアを配布する
be malicious if it's installing itself
自分自身をインストールしている場合は悪意のある
without his permission and without your
許可なく、あなたなしで
permission anyways who else would do
とにかく他の人が行う許可
that but malicious users how many of
悪意のあるユーザーが
them are based in Canada and subject to
それら は カナダに拠点を置き、
our Canadian for Yeah right you're not
私たちのカナダ人のために、 あなたはそうではあり ません
canadian websites most likely right does
カナダのウェブサイトが最も可能性が高い
it really have an impact but it might
それは本当に影響を与えますが、
just set the ball rolling right yeah the
ちょうど右に転がるボールを設定します。
updated rules are designed to protect
更新されたルールは、
Canadians from the most damaging and
最も被害を受けたカナダ人
deceptive form of spam and online
詐欺的な形式の迷惑メールとオンライン
threats without interfering with
妨げない脅威
legitimate businesses the revised rules
合法的なビジネスは改正されたルール
are targeting nuances such as adware on
アドウェアなどのニュアンスをターゲットにしています
PCs and rogue apps on smartphones false
スマートフォンでのPCや不正なアプリケーションの偽
or misleading representations of
または誤解を招く表現
products or services are also prohibited
製品やサービスも禁止されています
under the new regulations Canadians are
新しい規制の下でカナダ人は
encouraged to report suspected
疑わしいと報告するよう奨励した
violations of Canada's anti-spam laws to
カナダのスパム対策法違反
the spam Reporting Center at fight spam
迷惑メール対策のスパムレポートセンター
GCC a your place to go finally a ways to
GCCにあなたの場所は最終的に行く方法
go to report it I wonder if this it
それを報告するために行く私はそれがこれかどうか疑問に思う
would this have any bearing on say
これは、
Facebook and you're using the facebook
FacebookとあなたはFacebookを使用しています
app and you click on messages and says
あなたはメッセージをクリックして
you need to have such and such add up
あなたはそのようなものを追加する必要があります
but I guess if you consent and say okay
私はあなたが同意して大丈夫だと思う
if you don't then you don't get the
あなたが し なければ、あなた は
profit of the ability to send messages
メッセージを送る能力の 利益
so I guess it what good is it really
だから私 はそれが本当に 良いことを推測 する
it's all just legislation of people who
それはすべての人々の法律だけです
are not actually users who don't
実際にはないユーザーではありません
understand the technology and how it
技術とその理解方法
works and they say oh it looks good on
作品と彼らはああそれは上に見えると言う
paper you have to consent to install
あなたがインストールに同意しなければならない紙
this stuff but it really does nothing
このものは本当に何もしません
people blindly consent the things all
人々は盲目的にすべてのことに同意する
the time anyhow I know when I watch
とにかく私が腕時計を知っている時
people download apps they just didn't
人々はちょうど彼らがしなかったアプリをダウンロードする
even read through what they're agreeing
彼らが同意していることを読んでも
to and they just can
〜にすることができます
pages and pages of it exactly well the
それのページとページは正確に
good stuff is hidden in the fine print
良いものは細かいところに隠されている
all right one of the most glorious near
近く最も輝かしいの すべての権利1
misses in the history of British
英国の歴史の中でミス
exploration beacon to has been found the
探査ビーコンが発見された
british-built beacon to began its fall
英国製のビーコンが落ち始めた
to Mars on December nineteenth 2003 it
2003年12月19日に火星に
was expected to land on the red planet
赤い惑星に上陸する予定だった
on Christmas Day and began its search
クリスマスに
for alien life and begin at search for
外国人のために
alien life but it was never heard from
エイリアンの人生は聞こえませんでした
again the aliens may have found it now
もう一度エイリアンがそれを見つけたかもしれない
high-resolution images snapped over the
高解像度の画像が
last two years by NASA's Mars
NASAの火星が最後の2年間
Reconnaissance Reconnaissance Orbiter
偵察偵察機
shows the probe essentially to just
プローブを本質的にちょうど
where it ought to be within three miles
それは3マイル以内にあるべきです
of its target landing location it also
その目標着陸位置の
appears intact good job so what happened
元気でいい仕事に見えるので、何が起こったか
the theory base the theory based on the
理論は、理論に基づいて
images is that one or two of the probes
画像は、1つまたは2つのプローブ
four petals holding the solar panels did
ソーラーパネルを持っている4枚の花びらがやった
not deploy mission manager professor
ミッションマネージャー教授を配備しない
mark Sims says without full deployment
シムズは 完全な展開 なしに言う
there would have been no way we could
私たちができる方法はなかったでしょう
have communicated with it as the radio
ラジオとしてそれと通信している
frequency antenna was under the solar
周波数アンテナは太陽の下にあった
panels that's unfortunate i wonder if
残念なことに私は不思議なパネル
the antenna was not placed under the
アンテナは
panels whether or not even without the
パネルなしであってもなくても
panels it could have been communication
それが通信していたかもしれないパネル
there must have been a reason like it's
それのような理由があったに違いない
protecting it or something like a shell
それを保護するか、シェルのようなもの
yeah and then it's supposed to open up
ええ、その後、それは開く必要があります
but it didn't open up the antenna can
それはアンテナの缶を開けませんでした
pop up it's too bad sales any like
それはあまりにも悪い販売のような ポップアップ
there's a Oh pepek fail as a kid say
子供が言うように ああ pepekが失敗する
yeah while the probe can't be brought
ええ、プローブが持ち込まれないうちに
back to life professor Sims claims this
生命の教授シムズに戻ってこれを主張する
is not the end of the story they plan to
彼らが計画している話 の終わり ではない
do more imaging and an analysis but
より多くのイメージングと分析を行いますが
since the probe is intact the team can
プローブはそのままでチームは
be proud that they in fact were the
彼らが実際には
first to successfully penetrate Mars's
最初に火星に成功する
atmosphere and land on Mars even if they
火星の大気や土地さえあれば
couldn't continue from there so
そこから続けることができなかった
congratulations and way to go you've
おめでとうございます。
done it yeah the NASA website says that
NASAのウェブサイトによればそう
it was a failed mission but technically
それは失敗した使命だったが、技術的には
technically based on a technicality you
技術的に技術的にあなたに基づいて
landed on Mars yeah it's good way to go
火星に着陸したええ、それは良い方法だ
it completely not fail congratulations
それは完全にお祝いに失敗しない
you get at 50
あなたは50になる
well you got all the way there you
まあ、あなたはそこにい ます。
landed you go through the atmosphere a
あなたは大気を通って着陸した
forever accomplishment for sure for all
永遠の達成
your tech news with a slight Linux bias
わずかなLinuxの偏見であなたのハイテクニュース
visit the category 5 TV news room at
カテゴリ5のテレビニュースルームをご覧ください
newsroom category 5 TV for the category
ニュースルームカテゴリ5 カテゴリのテレビ
5 TV news room I'm Sasha taratus
5 TVニュースルーム私はSasha taratusです
enjoying the Sun in Jamaica thanks Sasha
ジャマイカで太陽を楽しむサシャ
this is category 5 technology TV you'll
これはカテゴリー5のテクノロジーTVです
find us online at triple w category five
私たちをtriple w category 5でオンラインで見つけよう
dot TV hello I'm Robbie Ferguson I'm
ドットテレビこんにちは私はロビーファーガソンです私は
Hillary rumble gay world here we are
ヒラリー・ランブルゲイ・ワールドはここ にいる
we're at our desk now and what a show
私たちは今、私たちの机にいます。
away it's been a great show busy show
離れてそれは素晴らしいショーの忙しいショーでした
fun fun fun I used to see so many people
楽しい楽しみ私はとても多くの人々を見ていました
in the chat room I was saying to the
チャットルームで私が に 言っていました
chat room there as sasha was telling us
サシャが私たちに言っていたようにチャットルームに
the news because roku is still
ロクがまだあるのでニュース
experiencing some little glitches here
ここに少しの不具合があります
and there we're working on that we
私たちはそこに取り組んでいます
really really really love you roku and
本当に本当に本当にあなたが Rokuの愛と
roku users we want to make this as good
私たちがこれを良いものにしたいと思うユーザー
as possible so if you're watching live
可能であればライブを見ている場合
on a roku stick around for about 15
約15ぐらいの周りの棒に
minutes after the show and i'm going to
ショー後数分、私は行くつもりです
stick around with you we're gonna have a
あなたと一緒にくっついて
little after show parte which is really
ショーparte後に少しは 本当に
just neat week instead settings and
代わりにちょうどきちんとした週と設定
you're gonna be my guinea pigs we're
あなたは私のモルモットになるよ
gonna see if we can get this thing
私たちがこの事を得ることができるかどうかを見て
licked all right so join me the chat
大丈夫だからチャットに参加する
room category five on freenode and fire
freenodeとfireの部屋カテゴリー5
up the live feed on your roku and we'll
あなたの 恋人の ライブフィードをアップしてください
be able to hopefully hopefully work this
うまくいけばうまくいけばこれを働かせることができる
out and next week we'll hear good
出かけると来週は良いことを聞くよ
reports right of course perfect that
もちろん、それを完璧に報告する
would be terrific would be thanks for
どうもありがとうございます
your monotonous input that would be
あなたの単調な入力は
terrific it would be due else is
素晴らしいそれは他の原因になります
terrific what is it answering people's
素晴らしいそれに答える人々のものです
questions I love it it makes that I'm
質問私はそれを愛し、それは私が いることになり
happy and it makes us happy knowing that
幸せと私たちはそれを知って幸せになります
we can help you first question coming to
私たちはあなたに最初に質問するのを助けることができます
us from strayer a striker is there a way
ストライカーからストライカーへの道がある
to embed a youtube channels upload feed
youtubeチャンネルのアップロードフィードを埋め込む
on a website using PHP embed a YouTube
PHPを使ったウェブサイトでYouTubeを埋め込む
channels uploads feed on that website
チャンネルはそのウェブサイトでフィードをアップロードします
using PHP nice
PHPのniceを使用して
that's a great question it is a great
それは素晴らしい質問です
that's an interesting question we've
それは面白い質問です
been we've been doing a little bit of
私たちはちょっとやっていたのですか？
programming on the show and what's
ショーのプログラミングと何が
interesting about this question is what
この質問について興味深いものは何ですか？
he's asking for specifically is a
彼は具体的に求めている
server-side way to bring in YouTube so
サーバー側でYouTubeを持ち込む方法
we're not talking jquery or youtube and
私たちはjqueryやyoutubeとは話していません。
beds or anything like that we're talking
私たちが話しているようなベッドや何か
about actually pulling it into PHP on
PHPを実際にPHPに取り込む方法について
the server and then you can do whatever
サーバーとあなたは何でもすることができます
you want with it because it's server
あなたはそれがサーバなのでそれで欲しい
side right so you can generate embed
右側に埋め込みを生成することができます
codes you can generate whatever you like
あなたが好きなものを生成できるコード
should we try to tackle this we've got
私たち は これに取り組もうとしなければなりません
about 14 minutes to the show so if I can
ショーに約14分かかります
do this in 14 minutes then I am
14分後にこれをやる
basically the champion I'd say what do
基本的にチャンピオン私は何を言うだろう
you think being of the world right here
あなたはここの世界にいると思います
champion there was only a song for that
チャンピオンはそのための曲しかなかった
that was not copy written okay I guess
それは私が推測する大丈夫と 書かれたコピーではなかった
I'm gonna do this hill all right I'm
私はこの丘をまっすぐにするつもりだ
ready I have for you I have officially
準備ができて私はあなたのために持っている 私は公式に
jumped into my temp folder so that's
私の一時フォルダに飛び込んだので
great watch PHP dash dash version I've
素晴らしい時計PHPのダッシュダッシュバージョン私は
got PHP installed awesome so I can use
私は使用できるようにPHPが素晴らしいインストールされている
this as a test bed so we don't have to
テストベッドとしてこれを行う必要はありません
do anything else alright so let's go
大丈夫だから行こう
touch my file dot PHP okay so we've just
私のファイルに触れるPHP 大丈夫
created a file called my file dot PHP
私のファイルdot PHPというファイルを作成しました。
let's edit it gonna do this in the
これを編集してみましょう
terminal haha how do you like that i'm
ターミナルハハ私はそれが 好き ですか？
using the nano text editor because i
私はナノテキストエディタを使用しているので
love how it has color eyes ations and
それがどのように色の目をしているかを愛し、
all that kind of stuff so we're going to
そのようなものはすべて私たちに行くつもりです
create a file that does stuff so hey hi
ちょっとこんにちは、こんにちは
there you go I've created the file I've
そこに行く私は私が作ったファイルを作成しました
saved it by hitting control oh you can
ああ、コントロールを打つことでそれを保存した
whatever you can use a text editor you
あなたがテキストエディタを使うことができるものは何でも
can use you could upload it to a server
それをサーバーにアップロードすることができます
and use however you want to do it I'm
しかし、あなたはそれをやりたい
just doing it this way because it's fun
それは楽しい ので、この方法でやっているだけです
and it's really really fast watch this
それは本当に本当に速いです
PHP my file dot PHP hi it says now if I
PHP私のファイルドットPHP
because that's what I told it to do if i
それは、私がもし私が
add a PHP end of line there it'll
そこにPHPの終わりを追加する
actually wrap the line okay so we know
実際に私たちが知っているので大丈夫な線をラップする
that PHP is working on my system I can
PHPが私のシステムで動いている
start working on stuff so what do we
私たちは何をしているのですか？
need to do we need to look at the
私たちは必要とする必要があり ます
the output of the YouTube API the
YouTube APIの 出力
application programming interface api
アプリケーションプログラミングインターフェイスAPI
api alright so let's do it so how do we
api 大丈夫ですので、どうしたらいいのですか？
do that well we'll go to google and
それをうまくやってgoogleと
we'll do a quick search for YouTube API
YouTube APIのクイック検索を行います
add video or no we don't want to add
追加したくないビデオを追加する
video we want to look at the users
私たちは ユーザー を見るビデオ
videos users video video feed types
動画ユーザー動画の動画フィードタイプ
second option there okay here you go
もう 2つ目のオプションがあります
there's the link that's easier just use
ちょっと使いやすいリンクがあります
google ok videos uploaded by a specific
特定のユーザーがアップロードした google okの動画
user we're going to use the API to get
ユーザーはAPIを使用して
that and you'll see that it gives you
それがあなたに与えられるのを見るでしょう
this URL for the JSON or XML response so
このJSONまたはXMLレスポンスのURL
if I copy that URL and paste it into my
その URL をコピー して
browser and then change user ID to the
ブラウザを開き、ユーザーIDを
user ID of the user that I want so let's
私はそうしてみましょうするユーザーのユーザーID
say category 5 TV now we get this
カテゴリ5のテレビが今これを取得すると言う
disgusting output of now this is not a
今のこの嫌な結果は、
JSON output you notice that it's XML it
JSON出力ではXMLであることがわかります
is but how can you tell because it's
あなたがどのように伝えることができるのですか？
just such a it's minified it's sloppy
ちょうどそのようなそれは細いそれが細かくなっている
crazy so I've copied that to my
狂ったので私はそれを私にコピーしました
clipboard ctrl a ctrl C then I'm going
クリップボードctrl ctrl Cその後私は行くよ
to go back to Google and I'm just going
Google に 戻って、私は ちょうど行くつもりです
to go XML pretteh fire Britta fication
XML pretteh fire Britta ficationに行く
fortification is a word that we use to
要塞化は、私たちが
make something pretty new it's like
かなり新しいものを作りなさい
making it pretty so first option that
それはかなり最初のオプションになります
comes up is XML beautifier that sounds
音が出るXML美化器が登場する
good let's paste our XML into there
さて、そこにXMLを貼り付けてみましょう
because that's gibberish and impossible
それは不器用で不可能なので
to read and let's beautify it any
読んでそれを美化させよう
beautifier pretty fire will work but you
美しい火事はうまくいくが、あなたは美しい
see what that did I have cleaned it up
私がそれをきれいにしたものを見てください
we can see tlk yep that's obviously nice
私たちはtlkを見ることができますねそれは明らかにいいです
clean XML now so you see now that we've
クリーンなXMLを今すぐ見て
done that that it did load category 5
カテゴリ5を読み込んだ
technology TV cool right and if I scroll
テクノロジーTVのクールな権利とスクロールすれば
down you'll start to see episodes of
あなたのエピソードを見始めるでしょう
category 5 TV there's episode number 382
カテゴリ5テレビエピソード番号382
viewer question extravaganza
ビューアの質問芸術祭
it's got the description it's got the
それはそれが持っている説明を持っている
files got the links it's got about
ファイルにはリンクがあります
everything right how cool is that that
すべてがいかにクールなのか
is cool PHP at least some of the the
クールなPHPは、少なくともいくつかの
newer versions includes access to
新しいバージョンには
creating Dom objects which is fantastic
素晴らしいDomオブジェクトを作成する
I don't want to go into what you know
私はあなたが知っているものに行きたくない
the technicality of what that means but
それが意味するものの専門性
basically simplifies the ability to pull
基本的にプルする能力を単純化する
data from other websites especially
特に他のウェブサイトからのデータ
through XML because that's what the the
これはXMLを使用しているためです
DOM is is going to be doing so what
DOMはそうするだろう
we're going to do is we're going to now
私たちは今行くつもりです。
now that we know that the API is able to
そのAPIが
generate this one xml output we're going
私たちが 行っ ている、この1つのXML出力を生成
to take this into PHP and do something
これをPHPに取り込んで何かする
with all this data look at it all right
このすべてのデータは大丈夫です
that's basically all our shows in her
それは基本的に彼女のすべてのショーです
life it is right there is this real life
人生は正しいです
okay so you see that there's my URL for
大丈夫ですので、私のURLがあります
the API and all I had to do was just
APIと私がしなければならなかったのはちょうど
paste in category 5 TV / user ID so I'm
カテゴリ5のテレビ/ユーザIDに貼り付けて
gonna copy that to my clipboard I'm
それを私のクリップボードにコピーするつもりです
gonna go back to nano and I'm going to
nanoに戻って、私は
create a new string called dollar sign
ドル記号と呼ばれる新しい文字列を作成する
URL and in ' brackets I'm going to paste
URLと ' 括弧内に貼り付けます
in that URL and end it with an
そのURLに
apostrophe semicolon do not fear i will
アポストロフィのセミコロンは恐れることはありません
upload the source code for this to the
これのためのソースコードを
web and you will have access to it
ウェブにアクセスすればアクセスできます
through the show notes of episode number
エピソード番号のショーノートを通して
383 okay carriage returns so now what do
383 大丈夫ですか？
I so now I've got the URL that we know
私は今私が知っているURLを持っています
contains the xml output of the YouTube
YouTubeのxml出力を含んでいます
API for the category 5 TV channel now we
カテゴリ5のテレビチャンネル用API
want to actually load it into the Dom so
それを実際に Dom にロードしたい
first we have to create a Dom object so
まずDomオブジェクトを作成する必要があります
we're going to go i'm going to call it
私たちは行くつもりです私はそれを呼び出すつもりです
RSS and that is going to become our
RSSとそれは私たちになるだろう
object now we're going to go new domme
オブジェクト今、私たちは新しいdommeに行くつもりです
all lowercase document semicolon okay so
すべての小文字の 文書セミコロン 大丈夫
we've just created a dom document in the
私たちはちょうど
object RSS now we're going to actually
オブジェクトのRSS今私たちは 実際に 行くつもりです
load the feed so we go dollar sign RSS
フィードをロードしてドル記号にするRSS
and then what are we going to do we're
私たちは何をするつもりなの？
going to load dollar sign URL
ドル記号のURLを読み込む
so we're loading the data from that xml
そのXMLからデータをロードしています
output from youtube nice and easy right
素敵で簡単なYouTubeからの出力
so now let's create an array we're going
それでは、配列を作成しましょう
to call this one our feed and we're
これを私たちのフィードと呼びます
going to say that this is just an empty
これはちょうど 空であると言うだろう
array because we need to define that
配列を定義する必要があるからです
erase that we don't generate any errors
エラーを発生させないように消去する
and let's loop through now that we know
私たちが知っているところで今すぐループしましょう
that RSS is now you know containing the
そのRSSは今あなたが知っている
information i'm not sure but if i do
情報私は確信していません が、もし私が
this let's see what happens yeah so see
これは何が起こるかを見てみましょう
that output it to the terminal because I
私は端末に 出力します
printed RSS to the screen so just so
スクリーンにRSSを印刷するだけで
that you can see that that's the same
あなたはそれが同じであることが分かります
data I've loaded it in okay now feed is
私はそれを大丈夫にロードしました
just an empty array and the reason for
空の配列とその理由
that is because we're going to create an
それは、私たちが
array that is going to contain all the
すべての配列を含む配列
data from that Dom object hmm it sounds
そのDomオブジェクトからのデータ
so fancy but you see how easy it is
すごく派手だけど、それがいかに簡単かを見る
right on the screen like don't don't let
右のように画面にはしないでください
the words that I speak throw you off
私が話す言葉はあなたを捨てる
look at the screen it is so simple look
とてもシンプルに見える画面を見てください
at that it sounds fandangled but it's
それは幻想的だと思うが、それは
actually really easy and so let's that
実際には本当に簡単です
now we've already learned about for each
今私たちは既にそれぞれについて学んだことがあります
so we're gonna do a for each loop right
私たちはそれぞれのループのために
that's a loop and we're going to loop
それはループであり、我々はループするつもりです
through RSS all right we want to go
私たちが望むすべての権利をRSSを通じて
through and we want to use the the Don
私たち はドン を使いたい
command get elements if I can type and
コマンドを入力して
talk at the same time get elements by
同時に話で要素を取得します
tag name now this is important we need
タグ名は今、これは我々が 必要とする ことが重要です
to know what are we actually looping
実際に何がループしているかを知る
through so we go back to our prettified
私たちは私たちのprettifiedに戻る
source code here you won't have to do
ここでソースコードを行う必要はありませ ん
this step because I'm going to do it
私はそれを行うつもりだからこのステップ
right now and I'm going to have the
今、 私は
answer for you it's going to be the same
あなたに答えてください。それは同じになるでしょう
for any feed that you look at what we
あなたが見ているフィードについては
want to go through is the by the ID
通過したいのは、IDによって
entry ok so that's the actual of the tag
エントリはOKなので、実際のタグです
name is called entry and then that is
名前はエントリと呼ばれ、それは
going to be one video and if I scroll
1つのビデオになり、 スクロールすると
down you'll see the end of the entry and
あなたはエントリーの終わりを見るでしょう
then another entry and this is another
別のエントリとこれは別のエントリです
video this is 381 now and if I scroll
ビデオこれは現在381です。スクロールすると
down it's going to close that entry and
その エントリ を閉じる 予定です
open another entry and that one it is
別のエントリーを開いてください
now 380
今380
ok so we're we're going to loop through
私たちはループする つもり です
the tag name entry in the Dom ok back to
ドームのタグ名の項目に戻る
our code here so that is so that's why I
私たちのコードはここにあるのでそうです
need to define that out now that we know
私たちが知っ ていること を 今それ を 定義する必要があります
it we're going to say entry ok so that's
それは我々がエントリokと言うことになるだろう
what we're going to go through make sure
私たちが通過を確認 するつもりです
that I've got my syntax right looks good
私の構文が正しいように見える
and we're going to call this node so
そして、私たちはそう、このノードを呼び出すする つもりです
we're defined it we're saying ok as we
私たちは、私たちが
loop through we're going to put the data
ループを通し、データを入れます
into an object called node so now let's
ノード と呼ばれるオブジェクトに
actually create our feed item we're
実際にフィードアイテムを作成する
going to say dollar sign item equals
ドル記号の項目が等しいと言うつもりです
array like that and I'm just kind of
そのような配列と私はまあまあです
facing things out in nano so that it
ナノの中に物を向けるように
makes sense and i'm going to call this
理にかなっていると私はこれを呼び出すつもりだ
title right and so i'm going to actually
タイトル権利と私は実際に行くつもりです
create that from the node of this off of
これをノードから作成する
this object so i'm going to say dollar
このオブジェクトので、 私はドルを言うつもりです
sign node remember I'm looping through
サインノードは私がループしていることを覚えている
so node for every episode is going to
すべてのエピソードのノードは
contain that episodes data so i'm going
そのエピソードデータを含んでいるので私は行くよ
to say node get we've already learned
to say私たちは既に学んだノードを取得する
this elements by tag name remember what
タグ名でこの要素は何を覚えている
that does it's the element by the tag
それはタグの要素です
name right it's pretty straight forward
それはかなりまっすぐ進む
speed then what do you want to do get
あなたが何をしたいのですか？
the elements by tag now that makes sense
タグで要素を理解することができます
ok so let's find out what the tag name
大丈夫だから、タグ名
is in our entry we want to grab the
私たちのエントリには、私たちは
title because that's what I'm creating
タイトルは私が作っているものなので
right so oh its title that's easy easy
そう簡単に簡単なタイトルです
ok back to our editor title title it's
エディタタイトルタイトルに戻ります
French it's we are from kinetic Canadian
フランス語それは私たちは運動のカナダ人です
so take tell we'll fix it so says title
だから私たちはそれを修正することを教えてくださいタイトルを言う
because that will actually not cause a
それは実際には
syntax error now this is where things
構文エラーは今、これはどこのものです
get kind of weird you got to say item 0
あなたがアイテム0と言うことができる奇妙なものを得る
because we want to define which item of
私たちは
the result we want to post in there is
私たちがそこに投稿したい結果があります
only one and one the first item in PHP
PHPの最初の項目は 1つだけです
is always 0 counting doesn't start at
常に0カウントは開始しない
one it starts at zero so the first item
1つはゼロから始まり、最初の項目
is item 0 ok and then we're going to use
アイテム0はOKですし、 次に使用する予定です
the node value of that you know I'm in a
私が知っているノードの価値
race so I don't put a semicolon so the
レースではセミコロンを入れないので
node value that I am pulling from all
私がすべてから引き離しているノードの値
this is going to be a sign
これはサインになるだろう
to title in the item array okay so now
アイテム配列のタイトルを大丈夫にする
if at the end of this I go and I say
これの終わりに私が行くと私は言う
print our dollar sign item notice I've
私たちドル記号の項目の通知を印刷する
created feed but I haven't decide
作成されたフィードが、私は決定していません
anything to it yet let's play clear my
それに何かまだ私のことをやってみよう
screen here clear command clear there
ここに画面クリアコマンドクリア
okay that's why I didn't work my file
大丈夫だから私は私のファイルを動かさなかった
dot PHP okay so did you see that it's
PHPは大丈夫 です
358 securing WordPress is what print our
358 ワードプレスを確保することは、
dollar sign item is and that's because
ドル記号の商品はそれで
it ran after the for each so it's the
それはそれぞれのために走ったので、それは
last one okay okay if I put that and
私はそれを置くと大丈夫最後の1つ
inside the loop it would output a whole
ループの内部では全体を出力します
bunch of them so we just did that to
それらの束は、私たちが それをした
test and make sure that item works oops
テストし、項目がうまく動作することを確認してください
okay next line now let's say we want to
大丈夫次の行は今私達 が
grab the URL because that's important to
URLを取得することは重要です
us right what am i doing sorry I hit
私たち右私は ヒット申し訳ありません 何をやっ ています
delete by accident there we go because
私たちが行くから事故で削除する
remember we're creating an array here so
ここで配列を作成していることを忘れないでください
the value of this array is title and URL
この配列の値はtitleとURLです。
those are the keys and now we're going
それらは鍵であり、今我々は行っている
to go dollar sign node we learned this
我々はこれを学んだドル記号ノードに行く
get elements by tag name how much time
タグ名で要素を取得する時間
we got hell we doing okay you got about
私たちは地獄になって大丈夫 です
two better here to Dan alright so what's
ここ2人がダンの方がいい
the link what's the link there it is
リンクはどこにありますか？
link can I just use link let's try it it
私はちょうどリンクを使用することができます それを試してみ ましょ う
has a bunch of them can I just pull one
彼らの束を持っている私はちょうど1つを引き出すことができます
let's see what test check link item 0 no
どのようなテストチェックリンク項目0を見てみましょう
value okay outside of that print our
それ以外の値は大丈夫です。
dollar sign item and exit
ドル記号の項目と終了
parse error you are what did I do oh
私は何をしたのですか？
forgot a comma I know I know punctuation
カンマを忘れてしまった私は、私は句読点を知っている知っています
saves lives it could definitely could oh
それは間違いなくオハイオ州にできる命を助ける
boy this is intense yeah we don't have
私たちは持っていないええ、これは激しい少年
time to really pull all the information
本当にすべての情報を引き出す時間
that we want to do but you can see where
私たちはやりたいことがありますが、あなたはどこで見ることができます
I'm going with it right this is a viewer
私はそれを見る人です
question I will gladly finish this code
質問このコードを喜んで終了します
but what I can what I wanted to do what
私は何をしたいのか
I was hoping to do I'm just gonna pull
私はちょうどつもりプルだ行うことを期待していました
back and just say okay we're gonna get
バックだけでは、我々はつもり大丈夫取得していると言います
the title so I've demonstrated yes yes
タイトル私はそれを実証したはいはい
you can grab it through PA nice okay in
あなたはPAで大丈夫です。
that loop we need to now assign dollar
そのループをドルに割り当てる必要があります
sign item two feet dollar sign feed
サインアイテム2フィートドル記号フィード
right we already created that array but
そのアレイを既に作成しています
how do we do that I i need to actually
どうやって私は私が実際にする必要がある
um i need to actually set that up right
私は実際にそれを設定する必要があります
let's pull it up I just want to get my
それを引っ張ってみましょう私はちょうど私を取得したい
syntax correct don't worries we're good
正しい構文であることを心配しないでください
are we wow really we could go all night
本当に私たちは一晩中行くことができた
really who's gonna stop us the viewers
本当に誰が私たちの視聴者を止めるつもりですか
love it they are eagerly waiting to see
熱心に待っているのが大好きです
what's going on here so no worries we're
何が起きて いるのか心配していない
good okay prevent our double our slang
良い大丈夫 私たちの二重のスラングを防ぐ
feed notice what I did is I did an array
私が何をしたのかをフィード通知する
push of dollars to an item into dollar
ドルへ のアイテムへのプッシュ
sign feed so what that does is it just
サインフィードはそうです
depends over and over and over again so
何度も何度も何度も
now my array contains all that stuff so
今私の配列にはすべてのものが入っているので
you can see with PHP now I'm gonna be
あなたはPHPで見ることができる今私はなる つもりだ
able to pull that data I can then parse
そのデータを取得することができます私は解析することができます
it I'm gonna figure you know you can get
それは私があなたが得ることができることを知っているつもりだ
the URL get the video file whatever you
URLはあなたのビデオファイルを取得します
want from the data we're completely out
私たちが完全に出ているデータから欲しい
of time that was an awesome question
すごい質問だった時間の
love it good question and I hope that
それは良い質問を愛し、私は願っています
I've been at least able to demonstrate
私は少なくとも実証することができました
yeah this is doable it might take a
ええ、これはなんとかですそれがかかる場合があります
little bit of tweaking here and there
ここやそこを少し微調整する
and figuring out the XML structure and
XML構造と
what tag names to use especially when
特に使用するタグ名
you've got the rel
あなたはrelを持っている
the various roles for each tag so we'll
各タグのさまざまな役割
work our way through those but well have
それらを通って私たちの道を歩く
fun happy programming yeah thanks
楽しいプログラミングええ、ありがとう
everybody and few great time tonight
今夜は誰もいなくてすばらしい時間
nice to see you and thank you so much
あなたとそんなにあなたに感謝を見て素敵
for being here tonight for the flight I
今夜私は飛行機に乗っています
think people should send in more
人々 がもっと送るべきだと思う
questions more fun stuff for us yes I so
質問私たちのためのより多くの楽しいものはい私はそう
keep them coming this email you like to
あなたが 好きなこのメールが来るようにしておいてください
receive emails she loves emails people
彼女は電子メールを愛する電子メールを受信する人々
live at category 5 TV if you want to
あなたがしたい場合はカテゴリ5のテレビでライブ
send an email get it into us your
メールをお送りください
questions are always welcome we love to
質問はいつも私たちが大好きです
hear from you and that don't get stick
あなたから聞いて、それは棒にならない
around after the show's manager on roku
ロクのショーのマネージャーの後で
live
ライブ
crazy lady until they jump up with the
彼らが跳躍するまで狂った女性
interview tonight yeah very well done oh
インタビュー今夜のええ非常によくやったああ
thank you how to be the man hair and all
どのように男の髪とすべてであることをありがとう、ありがとう
the work that you do and thank you at
あなたがしてくれてありがとう仕事
home for watching the show hope you have
あなたが持っているショーを見てホーム
a fantastic week don't forget to check
素晴らしい週はチェックすることを忘れないでください
out our website category 5
私たちのウェブサイトカテゴリ5
hair red shirt captain argento
キャプテンアルゼント、髪の赤いシャツ
we hope you enjoy the show category 5 TV
私たちはあなたがショー カテゴリ 5のテレビを楽しんで欲しい
broadcasts live from Barrie Ontario
ブロードキャストはBarrie Ontarioから放送されています
Canada every tuesday at seven pm eastern
火曜日ごとにカナダ東部標準時午後7時に
if you're watching this on demand or
オンデマンドでこれを見ている場合、または
through cable TV check out the local
ケーブルテレビでローカルをチェックアウト
show times in your area at category 5 TV
あなたのエリアの時間をカテゴリー5のテレビで見る
and find out when you can watch live and
あなたが生きているかどうかを見ることができます
interact in the community chat room
コミュニティチャットルームでやりとりする
category 5 is a production of prodigy
カテゴリ5は天才の生産です
digital solutions and is licensed under
デジタルソリューションのライセンスを受けています
creative commons attribution 2.5 canada
クリエイティブコモンズ帰属2.5カナダ
we'll see you next time thanks for
私たちはあなたのために次回のおかげが表示されます
tuning in
調整する